golden-gate-park.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
The following is the Privacy Policy of Running in the Rain that for the purposes of these terms is referred to as either RITR or GoldenGatePark.com.

Golden-Gate-Park.com supports a general policy of openness regarding personal data collection and use and so we have adopted this Privacy Policy as part of our commitment to protecting your personal information from misuse.

Golden-Gate-Park.com collects both personal information and aggregated information on our Web Sites.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You are under no obligation to provide personal information in order to use any of our services. We gather personal information only when you provide it to us for example in answering surveys; entering contests, quizzes and/or sweepstakes; registering as a site member; registering to receive information from us; purchasing products through our website; participating in message boards or chats; purchasing items via promotions or from us; and taking part in other promotional opportunities. You may be asked to provide your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address), financial information (such as credit card numbers), and demographic information (such as your Zip code, age, or income level).

Please note that sites to which you can link from Golden-Gate-Park.com (including any affiliated, co-branded or third party sites) may have different terms and conditions or policies applicable to those sites and we urge you to check the privacy policy and terms and conditions on each such site. Please also bear in mind that Golden-Gate-Park.com is not responsible for the content or the policies of any of these sites.  
Contact information is used to respond to your inquiries, to notify you if you have won a contest or a quiz and to send products and services ordered from our sites or sites, which are promoted from our sites. You also may receive periodic emails from us with information on new products and services, updates to our Web Sites or upcoming events.

Financial information that is collected is used only to process orders for products and services purchased through our Web Sites and is never shared with third parties for any other reason.

Demographic information is shared with advertisers and third parties only on an aggregated basis. (See the Aggregated Information Section below.)

Whenever we request your personal information on our Web Site, we will try to explain to you how we intend to use it and provide you with a choice to decline certain uses. In addition, if we plan to post any of your personal information on our Web Sites, other than usernames, (for example, your name and home town to identify you as the winner of a quiz), we will also use all reasonable efforts to notify you of this possibility either when you provide information to us or prior to posting the information. We may also be required to disclose personal information pursuant to valid legal process.

 **AGGREGATED INFORMATION**  
We gather information through our Web Site relating to traffic levels on our Web Site – for example, the total number of users visiting particular pages. We may also aggregate demographic information and the results of surveys.

We use IP addresses to calculate Web site usage levels. Whenever you are on the Internet, a number (an IP address) is automatically assigned to your computer. This number is identified and logged automatically whenever you visit our Web Sites. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice on the Internet, and is done automatically by many Web sites. An IP address does not provide us with any of your personally identifiable information, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us.

This aggregated information, which does not personally identify you, is helpful to us for improving the services we offer and for marketing purposes. We may share aggregated information with our advertisers, business partners, or other companies.

 **USE OF COOKIES BY GOLDEN-GATE-PARK.COM**  
Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including ours, can facilitate a user’s ongoing access to and use of a site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files.  
We may use cookies to track your preferences on our website. We may also use a cookie to track the products you have chosen to purchase while shopping on our Web Sites. The cookie saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again during multiple or single visits.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline or accept the cookie feature. You should note, however, that declining the cookies may make it difficult for you to make purchases on our Web Sites and will make entering our discussion areas more burdensome.

 **COMMENTS AND DISCUSSION FORUMS**  
We have use comment areas, and may have discussion areas and chat forums available to our users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Whenever you contribute to a comment or discussion area, your screen name will automatically display but your email address will not.

 **CHILDREN**  
We do not direct any of our content specifically at children under thirteen (13) years of age. Please note that nowhere on the Site do we knowingly collect profile information from children under the age of 13.

 **THIRD-PARTY AD SERVING**  
The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry or our advertisers who choose to employ a third party adserver may in the course of serving advertisements place or recognize a unique cookie. Through cookie technology, advertisers may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you. This information may be used to deliver tailored ads to you. We do not control this process, and these cookies are subject to the third party adserver and the advertisers’ policies. However, these third parties do not obtain, through use of cookies or otherwise, any personally identifiable information from us or from any of our Web Sites.

 **SECURITY**  
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. We may use third parties to host and maintain our Web Sites.

 **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  
Our Web sites may contain links to third-party Web sites. The linked sites are not under the control of GoldenGatePark.com, and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. We are providing these links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site by GoldenGatePark.com.

 **CHOICE/OPT-OUT**  
We give you the following options for:

• informing us that you wish to stop receiving future email communications from our Web Sites; or

• informing us of changes to the personal information you have previously provided so we can correct or update the information we hold:

You can send email to us via the “[Contact]” form located at goldengatepark.com/contact/.

Please note: We are not responsible for removing information from third-party lists or entities with which you have shared your information pursuant to this policy.

 **REVISIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY**  
Any of the policies or procedures above may be changed at any time without prior notice. Although this Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights, it does serve as an expression of our commitment to protecting private personal information.
